

Contact

Phone

+959986923318

Email

zawnayla.znl@gmail.com

Linkedin

http://www.linkedin.com/in/zaw-nay-la

Expertise

- Dart, Flutter
- React Js, Next Js
- Angular
- Python
- Node Js
- Vue Js

Cloud Service

- AWS
- Digital Ocean
- Vercel

Language

English

Japanese

Burmese

Zaw Nay La

Software Developer

A computer science enthusiast with a deep love for technology and problemsolving. So Far, I am a full stack developer with 3+ years of hands-on experience. An enthusiast with passions, dedications and eagerness to be part of emerging technological advancements.

Experience

July 2024 - Present

Free Lance

Font-End Developer

- Deploy and maintain full-stacked web application using Angular, React and Vue.js
- Maintain high standards of quality in both codes and processes, conducting reviews every weeks
- Learn and improve languages and create peculiar projects for higher quality and skills

August 2022 - July 2024

Myanmar Information Technology Co., Ltd (MIT)

Full-Stack Developer

- Developed responsive and intuitive user experience websites using javascript and angular framework
- Collaborated with senior developers for cleaner, efficient and well-documented projects
- Maintained projects quality with task driven development (TDD)
- Managed production-level projects which have +3k daily active users

🗘 Jan 2021 - June 2022

TASTYSOFT Software Outstanding Co.,Ltd

Flutter/Web Developer

- Participated in development of the SchoolFlow Financial Statement Project utilizing Dart and Flutter Framework.
- Collaborated with the team lead and senior developers on UI/UX Design
- · Conducted testing and debugging of web applications

Education

Mandalay Software Institute (MSI)

2021-2022

Former Student at University of Medicine, Mandalay

2017-2020

Key Projects

Neo Team

Human resource management system for managing the employee life cycle.

Used Tech: React, PostgresSQL,AWS

Features : Recruiting, hiring, onboarding, salary, promotion and firing employees

KHUB

Online learning/teaching platform which includes two sites, one for the learners and one called Khub Studio for the instructors

Used Tech: Angular 13, Flutter, Python, DynamoDB

Features : Responsive and quick interactive courses with payments, quizzes and certificate.

Gold Shop

Services that sources products from suppliers and sells those products to both retail and wholesale customers.

Used Tech: Flutter, Node Js, Digital Ocean

Features : Buy and sell product with up-to-date daily price rate, billing and invoicing, multi-level assessment

and permissions.

Sky Clinic

Connect patients with various clinics and doctors. Features include for both clinics and patient.

Used Tech: Flutter, Node Js, Digital Ocean

Features : Patients registration and management, appointment scheduling electronic health recording,

billing and invoicing

IAM

Identity and Access Management System which is responsible for user authentication and authorization processes.

Used Tech: Python, PostgresSQL, RDS

PMS

Property Management System(PMS) for manage the day-to-day operations of their properties

Used Tech: Angular 13, Python, AWS

Features : Commercial use, properties management, rental payment and tenant communicatio

.